Hello
hello friends welcome to all the friends
Larsen & Toubro Infotech Limited i.e.
NTI's Water For results have come
here first of all you should see the company has
announced a difference by sharing it at 30 rupees for its health but this
is the final difference so later only the
approval of the boy is required which will be
obtained in their exam so there is
no need to worry now we go to the company's
director result here I will
fill a little bit so that time is available children now
we have come to the company's result here first of all
you should see the numbers you will
see clearly this is this time i.e.
Water For's number and this is the
previous quarter i.e. Water Three's number
and this is the previous year's quarter four's number
I will zoom in and arrange it
so that you can see the numbers clearly I hope that
you are able to understand clearly now here we will
first start with the revenue from
operations which this time is 42 thousand
sixteen and its previous quarter i.e. Water
Three was 41 thousand 376 which is what
Unique Water For had done last year
In the quarterly figures of 2019, it was 32000
694, so you can say that
this year is looking quite good as compared to last year
and the quarterly under water is also
seeing a good increase, if
other income is added to it then the
total income of MTI this time will be
44306, which in the last quarter's under water
was 42000 375 and in the previous year's
under water it was 33 thousand 724, so a significant increase is being
seen in the income of the company
and a good increase in the quarterly under water is also being
seen, it is a very good
thing, the income of the company is
looking very good here, now let's take a
look at the expenses as well, here the
list of expenses is given, if you want you
can see both the expenses together, now we add the
total expenses here,
this time the total expense of MTI is 35
thousand seven hundred sixty, which in the previous quarter
was 34102 38 and in the previous year's quarter  The
form was
26556, so you can say that the expenses have increased year after year
and a slight increase is also being seen quarter after quarter.
No problem, when income increases then expenses also increase, it is a
natural thing, the problem arises when expenses
increase beyond limit, then due to that the
profit starts decreasing, at present this is
not the case in NTI case, hence there is no need to worry.
Now see here, the profit
gift act means that after incurring expenses and
before paying taxes, what is left in the hands of the company is Rs
8,596, which
was Rs 8,233 in the previous quarter and Rs
7,000,168 in the quarter for the previous year, but this is
not net profit, there will be a text
adjustment in it, after that
what remains with the company will be this time's NPR card
profit. Now see here, this time's
net profit of the company is written, I will
zoom it so that it is
understood very clearly, after expressing everything,
after paying taxes, what is left in the hands of the company is Rs
6375 of NTI.  Aishwarya's net profit which
was 6125 in the last quarter and
5400 in the quarter for last year seventy five
friends, the company's profit has increased a lot this year compared to
last year and this quarter is
also seeing a good increase
in the company's profit a little bit now let's
check the CTS at the end, I will
adjust it a little bit yes now it
is clear this GPS this time the IPS is 36
point 342 last quarter it was 34
point ninety five and last year in the quarter for it
was 31 point 22 if the company is profitable
then the company's EPS will also increase it is a very
good thing
so according to me NTI's quarter
for result was very good if you
have this city then you can easily fold it so then that's all the
information for now if you liked it then definitely give this video
a like and if you are
new to this channel then subscribe to this channel
because we keep bringing updates related to the stock market
on this channel so we will
meet in the next video then  goodbye till